

# Contact \_\_Info



+62 812 8386 2455



Jalan Pendidikan II no. 28, RT001/RW006 Pssar Rebo, East Jakarta 13770 Indonesia



ryosangvegmail.com



LinkedIn: rio-anggara



Facebook: ryosang.vanjava



Twitter: eriosangvanjava

# RIO ANGGARA

I am a sales and marketing expert with over seven years of experience. My skills include leadership, time management, social media marketing, teamwork, communication, Microsoft Office, direct sales, and passive English. My hobbies include travelling and automotive.

## PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

#### AREA SALES MANAGER

PT. AEON CREDIT SERVICE | 2019 - PRESENT

- Managing recruiting, objectives setting, coaching and performance monitoring of sales team
- Utilize sales promotion by giving socialization to be applied by the internal team
- Designing and implementing a strategic sales plan that expands company's customer base and ensure it's strong presence

#### SALES AND MARKETING

PT. MOBILKAMU.COM | 2019 - 2019

Responsible in overseeing the sales and marketing of all units and all brands.

#### DISTRICT SALES MANAGER

PT. HOMECREDIT INDONESIA | 2016 - 2018

- Supervising a team of sales agents
- Responsible in ensuring the sales target for agents are achieved
- Developing strategies to achieve sales target
- Writing daily, weekly, and monthly reports
- Maintaining good relationship with partnering store dealers
- Offering partnerships with new store dealers

#### SALES AGENT

PT. HOMECREDIT INDONESIA | 2015 - 2016

Responsible for sales and marketing directed to consumers who are looking to apply credits for cellphone, electronics, furniture, etc.

#### MARKETING EXECUTIVE

PT. DIAMONDLAND DEVELOPMENT | 2014 - 2015

Responsible in overseeing the sales and marketing of all housing units.

#### GENERAL AFFAIRS STAFF

PT. CIPTA TELEVISI INDONESIA (MNCTV) | 2013 - 2014

- Listing inventory for company's assets
- Procuring office equipments including stationary, desks, chairs, laptops, etc.

## EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

### BINA SARANA INFORMATIKA

DIPLOMA III MANAJEMEN INFORMATIKA | 2008 - 2013